[{"answer": "Well, I'm doing great, Piers, thank you so much.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Senator, how are you?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "No, no harboring of any aspirations.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "Were you harboring any inspirations to be the last- minute VP?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I have a lot of respect for Paul.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "So you two couldn't be further apart, really, could you?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Well, the interesting thing here is the facts actually are on our side when it comes to, you know, making the pitch to the American people.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "How are you going to ensure as a party that your message wins the day?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Well, the financial crisis really wasn't related to the tax cuts.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "If tax cuts are the answer, why did we end up after eight years of George Bush with the financial crisis we ended up with?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "Well, there's a lot of evidence to it.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Is it actually going to work?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Well, no, because we had a financial meltdown.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "What was the rate on the date he left?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "Well, no, I understand that.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "But -- to be -- but to be fair, you can't quote 4 percent when his final percentage was what?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "The linkage -- I don't -- I don't remember.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "Yes, but what was it?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "Well, I agree with that first thing he said about, hello and thank you for having me on the show.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "What did you make of what Senator Santorum was tub thumping away there with?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Anything else ?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "I think it is.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "That is the Democrat view, isn't it?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "The Democrats must be a little bit worried, aren't they, that this bandwagon currently rolling, the Romney/Ryan bandwagon, could resonate to a victory in November?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "Two uniforms and a set of car bombs.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "Who found the body?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "Looks like half of Manhattan handed this door.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Yes, you got prints?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "You ever think your friends who place with valet parking and accused you of some stranger?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "That's a very good question.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Or is the purpose of the book to put out enough doubt to make people just question, again, the veracity of what they've been told?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "Well, the scientific evidence is overwhelming.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "And if so, by who and why?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "Well, it wasn't the Kennedys, which is, you know, some people would think.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "What is your theory about who may have killed her?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Well, I know what happened, and so do you and it's all in the public domain.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "So what do you believe happened?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Because you're grouping that with this.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "And if I said we didn't, would you summarily dismiss everything I said before that?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "And about being brilliant, yes, why not?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "Hi, Piers.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Welcome, P.J. How are you?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Hi, P.J.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "No, I'm not.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Before we go on to politics, are you a -- are you a natural conspiracy theorists yourself, P.J.?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "On your show?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "With you?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "P.J., over to you.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Which Democrat brought this country to its knees?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "I'm doing great.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Hope, how are you?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "As a British man, do you appreciate goal keeping?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "Well, let's talk about before I made the save.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "When you made the save, what goes through your mind?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "We've come a long way, let's be honest.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "Why is that, do you think?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "Yeah, you know what, that's not true though.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "It's also not unhelpful that you radiate beauty yourself, is it, Hope?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "OLO: It's not really the most important thing.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "What was the most important thing that you wanted to get out there about that whole time?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "I think you're slightly overdoing the whole bad wrap thing.", "docId": "120814pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "You think I'm being hard on myself?", "qSentId": 686}]